Edwin J. Feulner Papers
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Heritage Foundation, 1953-2013 (Box 138-517)
  - Correspondence
    - General
      - 1997
        - Feb.-Apr., (11 folders) (Box 280)
        - May-June, (7 folders) (Box 281)
        - July, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 282)
        - Aug.-Sept., (8 folders)
        - Oct.-Nov., (9 folders) (Box 283)
        - Dec., (4 folders) (Box 284)
      - 1998
        - Jan.-Feb., (5 folders)
        - Mar., (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 285)
        - Apr., (5 folders)
        - May, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 286)
        - June, (3 folders)
        - July, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 287)
        - Aug.-Sept., (6 folders)
        - Oct., (2 folders) (Box 288)
        - Nov.-Dec., (6 folders)
      - 1999
        - Jan., (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 289)
        - Feb.-Mar., (6 folders)
        - Apr.-May, (6 folders) (Box 290)
        - June, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 291)
        - July-Aug., (4 folders)
        - Sept., (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 292)
        - Oct.-Dec., (6 folders)
      - 2000
        - Jan., (1 folder) (Box 293)
        - Feb.-Mar., (5 folders)
        - Apr., (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 294)
        - May-June, (7 folders)
        - July, (1 folder) (Box 295)
        - Aug.-Dec., (9 folders)
      - 2001 (Box 296)
        - Jan.-Apr., (10 folders)
        - May-Aug., (7 folders) (Box 297)
        - Sept., (1 folder) (Box 298)
        - Oct.-Dec., (5 folders)
      - 2002
        - Jan., (2 folders)
        - Feb., (1 folder) (Box 299)
        - Mar., (4 folders)
        - Apr., (2 folders) (Box 300)
        - May-July, (7 folders)
        - Aug.-Nov., (9 folders) (Box 301)
        - Dec. (Box 302)
      - 2003
        - Jan.-Mar., (8 folders)
        - Apr.-July, (7 folders) (Box 303)
        - Aug.-Dec., (7 folders) (Box 304)
      - 2004
        - Jan., (1 folder) (Box 305)
        - Feb.-Apr., (7 folders)
        - May-Aug., (7 folders) (Box 306)
        - Sept., (1 folder) (Box 307)
        - Oct.-Dec., (7 folders)
      - 2005 (Box 308)
        - Jan.-Apr., (8 folders)
        - May-Sept., (9 folders) (Box 309)
        - Oct.-Dec., (5 folders) (Box 310)
      - 2006
        - Jan.-Feb., (3 folders)
        - Mar.-May, (8 folders) (Box 311)
        - June-Sept., (8 folders) (Box 312)
        - Oct.-Dec., (5 folders) (Box 313)
      - 2007
        - Jan.-Feb., (3 folders)
        - Mar.-May, (8 folders) (Box 314)
        - June, (1 folder) (Box 315)
        - July-Nov., (7 folders)
        - Dec., (2 folders) (Box 316)
      - 2008
        - Jan.-Mar., (5 folders)
        - Apr., (1 folder) (Box 317)
        - May-Aug., (5 folders)
        - Sept.-Dec., (4 folders) (Box 318)
      - 2009
        - Jan.-Feb., (3 folders)
        - Mar., (1 folder) (Box 319)
        - Apr.-June, (4 folders)
        - July, (1 folder) (Box 320)
        - Aug.-Dec., (5 folders)
      - 2010
        - Jan.-Feb., (2 folders)
        - Mar.-Aug., (7 folders) (Box 321)
        - Sept.-Dec., (4 folders) (Box 322)
      - 2011
        - Jan.-Mar., (3 folders)
        - Apr.-Nov., (8 folders) (Box 323)
        - Dec. (Box 324)
      - 2012
        - Jan.-Aug., (9 folders)
        - Sept.-Dec., (4 folders) (Box 325)
      - 2013
        - Jan.-July, (7 folders)
        - Aug.-Dec., (5 folders) (Box 326)
    - Internal memoranda
      - 1978-1982, (5 folders)
      - 1983, (2 folders) (Box 327)
      - 1984-1988, (6 folders)
      - 1989, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 328)
      - 1990, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box 329)
      - 1991, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box 330)
      - 1992
      - 1993
        - Jan.-June, (6 folders)
        - July-Dec., (7 folders) (Box 331)
      - 1994
        - Jan.-Apr., (2 folders)
        - May-Nov., (6 folders) (Box 332)
        - Dec. (Box 333)
      - 1995
        - Jan.-May, (6 folders)
        - June-Oct., (6 folders) (Box 334)
        - Nov.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 335)
      - 1996
        - Jan.-Feb., (4 folders)
        - Mar., (1 folder) (Box 336)
        - Apr.-Aug., (5 folders)
        - Sept.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box 337)
      - 1997
        - Jan.-Mar., (3 folders)
        - Apr.-July, (5 folders) (Box 338)
        - Aug., (1 folder) (Box 339)
        - Sept.-Dec., (4 folders)
      - 1998
        - Jan.-Feb., (2 folders)
        - Mar.-Aug., (7 folders) (Box 340)
        - Sept.-Dec., (4 folders) (Box 341)
      - 1999
        - Jan.-Feb., (3 folders)
        - Mar.-July, (8 folders) (Box 342)
        - Aug., (1 folder) (Box 343)
        - Sept.-Dec., (6 folders)
      - 1990s
      - 2000
        - Jan., (2 folders)
        - Feb.-May, (8 folders) (Box 344)
        - June-Dec., (10 folders) (Box 345)
      - 2001 (Box 346)
        - Jan.-May, (6 folders)
        - June-Dec., (8 folders) (Box 347)
      - 2002
        - Jan.-Feb., (2 folders)
        - Mar.-Sept., (8 folders) (Box 348)
        - Oct., (1 folder) (Box 349)
        - Nov.-Dec., (2 folders)
      - 2003
        - Jan.-May, (5 folders)
        - June-Dec., (10 folders) (Box 350)
      - 2004 (Box 351)
        - Jan.-May, (10 folders)
        - June-Oct., (9 folders) (Box 352)
        - Nov.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 353)
      - 2005
        - Jan.-June, (7 folders)
        - July-Dec., (8 folders) (Box 354)
      - 2006
        - Jan., (2 folders)
        - Feb.-Oct., (11 folders) (Box 355)
        - Nov.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 356)
      - 2007
        - Jan.-June, (8 folders)
        - July-Dec., (8 folders) (Box 357)
      - 2008 (Box 358)
        - Jan.-May, (9 folders)
        - June-Dec., (9 folders) (Box 359)
      - 2009 (Box 360)
        - Jan.-July, (9 folders)
        - Aug.-Dec., (8 folders) (Box 361)
      - 2010
        - Jan.-Feb., (2 folders)
        - Mar.-Dec., (12 folders) (Box 362)
      - 2011 (Box 363)
        - Jan.-Sept., (9 folders)
        - Oct.-Dec., (3 folders) (Box 364)
      - 2012
        - Jan.-Apr., (4 folders)
        - May-Dec., (9 folders) (Box 365)
      - 2013
        - Jan.-Feb., (2 folders)
        - Mar.-Dec., (10 folders) (Box 366)
    - Members of Congress
      - 1977, (2 folders)
      - 1978, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 367)
      - 1979-1989, (11 folders)
      - 1990-1998, (10 folders) (Box 368)
      - 1999-2000, undated (Box 369)
    - Miscellaneous
      - 1972-1984, (9 folders)
      - 1985-1995, (10 folders) (Box 370)
      - 1996, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 371)
      - 1997-2003, (9 folders)
      - 2004-2013, (10 folders) (Box 372)
      - 2000s
      - Undated
    - White House
      - 1982-1989
      - 1990-1992, undated, (2 folders) (Box 373)
  - Council on Foundations, 1999
  - Cyberport, Hong Kong (China), 1999
  - Departmental goals, 1993, (2 folders)
  - Development Office
    - Call reports and contributions, 1993-1999, 2009, (6 folders)
    - Development and fund-raising priorities, 2010-2012, (1 folder) (Box 374)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997
    - Weekly meeting agendas, 2008-2009
  - Dinners given by Holland Hanson ("Holly") Coors, 1990
  - Direct mail, 1981-1986, 1995-1996, 2001
  - Distribution, 1977, (5 folders)
  - Donald Devine Project, 1994
  - Educational Research Trust, 1985-1986 (Box 375)
  - Estate gifts
    - Blackwell, William G., antiques, 1976-1979, (2 folders)
    - Josephson, Emanuel, 1997
  - Ethics Resource Center, 1980, undated
  - European Communities, travel grant application, 1974-1979
  - Federal budget chart books, 2011-2012
  - Federal Election Campaign Act and Laws, 1972-1976, (3 folders)
  - Feulner, Edwin J.
    - Early files
      - 1973-1974
      - 1975-1976, (10 folders) (Box 376)
      - 1977, undated, (2 folders) (Box 377)
    - Expense statements, 1977-1979, (4 folders)
    - Feulner's laws, 2010
    - Memoranda to the files, 1973-1976
    - Notebooks
      - 1977-1981, (2 folders)
      - 1983-1997, (6 folders) (Box 378)
      - 1998, (4 folders); (1 folder) (Box 379)
      - 1998-2005, (6 folders)
      - 2004-2008, (4 folders) (Box 380)
      - 2008-2013, undated, (5 folders) (Box 381)
    - Twentieth anniversary as president of Heritage Foundation, 1997
  - Fike, Elmer, correspondence, 1974
  - Filibuster, 1975, 2008-2010
  - Finance and operations reviews, 1999
  - Financial proposals
    - Bank of New York, 1996 (Box 382)
    - Biltmore Prime Cash Management Fund, 1995
    - Boatmen's Trust Company, 1992-1995, undated, (3 folders)
    - Donors Trust, 2004
    - Goldman Sachs, 2007
    - Miscellaneous, 1996
    - Pacific Investment Management Company, 2004
    - PNC Bank, 1996
    - Pro-Pharmaceuticals, 2002
    - State Street Bank and Trust Company, 1995-1996, (3 folders) (Box 383)
    - U.S. Trust Company of New York, undated
    - Wachovia, 1996, (2 folders)
    - Washington Capital Partners, 2000 (Box 384)
    - Wilmington Trust, 1992-1996, (2 folders)
    - Zurich Financial Services, 2001
  - Financial records
    - Bank reports, 1996-1997
    - Cash reports
      - 1979-1989 (3 folders
      - 1990-2001, (3 folders) (Box 385)
    - Monthly reports
      - 1978-1981, (2 folders)
      - 1982-1984, (5 folders) (Box 386)
      - 1985-1987, (5 folders) (Box 387)
      - 1988-1991, (5 folders) (Box 388)
      - 1993, (3 folders) (Box 389)
      - 1994, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 390)
      - 1995, (3 folders)
      - 1996-2000, (2 folders) (Box 391)
  - Foghorn Group, 1975
  - Foreign Affairs Research Institute, 1977-1984, (3 folders)
  - Foreign aid and the United States Agency for International Development, 1980-1985, undated
  - Fraser Institute, Walker-Gwartney feud, 1996-1998
  - Frontiers for Freedom, 1995
  - "Fundraising: Cultivation and Solicitation Strategy," 1996
  - Gingrich, Newt, meetings with, 1997-1999, (4 folders) (Box 392)
  - Goals, 1995-1996, (2 folders)
  - Hanyang University, Seoul (Korea)
    - 1988-2004, (2 folders)
    - Undated (Box 393)
  - Health care
    - General, 1992-1999, 2007-2009, undated, (3 folders)
    - Goodman, John C., 1994
    - Financial Impact of the Health Security Act, 1993
    - Health Care Reform by the Numbers, 1993 (Box 394)
  - Henry Salvatori Foundation, 1991-1997, undated
  - Herbold, Robert J., memoranda and correspondence, 2002-2013
  - Heritage 10: Funding the Conservative Decade, 1983-1985, undated
  - Heritage Action for America, 2006-2012
  - High Frontier Project, 1981-1989
  - Hillsdale College, Hillsdale, Mich., 1975-1984, 1990-1995, 2000-2006, undated
  - Hinckley Institute of Politics, internships with Heritage Foundation, 1998 (Box 395)
  - Hodge, Scott, "Heritage Plan: Family Tax Relief," undated
  - Hutchinson, John, visiting scholar, 1978-1979, (3 folders)
  - Income tax return, 1987
  - Index for Economic Freedom
    - General
      - 1995-1998, (7 folders)
      - 1999, 2012, (4 folders) (Box 396)
    - Research, 1996-2003, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 397)
  - Index of Leading Cultural Indicators, 1993
  - Information Marketing Department, 1996-1997, undated, (2 folders)
  - Inside the Hill, newsletters, 1997-2000
  - Institute for Policy Research, Kuala Lumpur Project, 1998, undated
  - Institute for the Study of Conflict
    - 1978-1979, (3 folders)
    - 1980-1982 (Box 398)
  - Institute of Economic Affairs, 1992-2009, undated, (2 folders)
  - Institute of International Relations, 1986-1989, undated, (5 folders)
  - Institute of World Politics, 1991-1992, undated
  - Institute on Strategic Trade, 1978
  - Internal Revenue Service See Legal records
  - Interns, 1997-1999, 2006-2011, undated, (3 folders)
  - Issue assignments, 1981 (Box 399)
  - James Madison Foundation, 1974-1976, 1989
  - Japan External Trade Organization, 1986-1986, undated
  - Job descriptions, 1998
  - Joint Committee on Taxation, 1997-1998
  - Korea at the United Nations, 1973-1975
  - Korea Foundation, Seoul (Korea), 1997-1998
  - Law and Economics Center, University of Miami, Coral Gables, Fla., 1978-1984
  - Lawrence Fertig boardroom, 1987-1989, undated
  - Leadership for America, 2007-2011, undated
  - Legal records See also Containers 423-425, McKenna v. Heritage Foundation
    - Articles of incorporation, bylaws, and tax-exempt status, 1976
    - Exhibits concerning Mary Baker Eddy: Her Spiritual Footsteps (Carpenter Foundation)
    - General
      - 1976-1977, 1983-1992, (2 folders)
      - 1996-1999, 2010, undated, (2 folders) (Box 400)
    - Internal Revenue Service, audit and investigation, 1978-1979, (4 folders)
    - Public Citizen, infringement, 1996-1997
  - Lehrman Center for Monetary Policy, 2011
  - Library Court Group See Containers 138-144, Administrative memoranda
  - Mailing list, additions and corrections, 1978-1980
  - Mailings
    - Dear Ed letters
      - 1977-1979
      - 1980-1991, (7 folders) (Box 401)
      - 1992-1998, (7 folders) (Box 402)
      - 1999-2009, (7 folders) (Box 403)
      - 2010-2012, undated, (5 folders) (Box 404)
    - Dear Editor letters
      - 1977-1979, (3 folders)
      - 1980-1981, (5 folders) (Box 405)
      - 1982, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 406)
      - 1983, (3 folders)
      - 1984, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 407)
      - 1985, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 408)
      - 1986-1987, (6 folders)
      - 1988-1994, (7 folders) (Box 409)
      - 1995-1998, (5 folders) (Box 410)
    - General
      - 1973-1981, (2 folders)
      - 1982-1992, (6 folders) (Box 411)
      - 1993-2001, (7 folders) (Box 412)
      - 2002-2009, (6 folders) (Box 413)
      - 2010-2012, undated, (6 folders) (Box 414)
  - Major projects, weekly listings (Box 415)
    - 1977-1981, (8 folders)
    - 1982-1983, (6 folders) (Box 416)
    - 1984-1985, (6 folders) (Box 417)
    - 1986-1988, (6 folders) (Box 418)
    - 1989-1991, (6 folders) (Box 419)
    - 1992-1993, (3 folders) (Box 420)
  - Management manual, 1979
  - Mandate for Leadership: Policy Management in a Conservative Administration
    - Executive summary report, 1981
    - Miscellaneous, 1980, undated
    - Project team reports, 1980 (Box 421)
      - Circulation copy
      - Miscellaneous, (2 folders)
    - Summary report on presidential executive orders, 1980 (Box 422)
  - Mandate for Leadership II: Continuing the Conservative Revolution, 1984-1985, undated
  - Mandate for Leadership III: Policy Strategies for the 1990s
    - Media coverage, 1989
    - Miscellaneous, 1988-1989
    - Outline and Task Force status sheet, 1988-1989
    - Page proofs, circa 1989, (2 folders)
  - Mandate for Leadership IV: Turning Ideas into Actions, 1997, undated
  - McKenna v. Heritage Foundation (Box 423)
    - Appendices and exhibits, 1976, undated
    - General case material
      - 1974-1975
      - 1976
        - Mar.-Sept., (6 folders)
        - Oct.-Dec., (2 folders) (Box 424)
      - 1977
        - Jan.-Apr., (4 folders)
        - May-Dec., (4 folders) (Box 425)
      - 1978-1979, undated
  - Meetings file
    - Management retreat, 1980
    - Miscellaneous, 1979, 1988-2011
    - Senior management
      - 1987-1990, (3 folders)
      - 1991-1998, (8 folders) (Box 426)
      - 1999-2001, (5 folders) (Box 427)
      - 2002, (1 folder); (3 folders) (Box 428)
      - 2003, (3 folders)
      - 2004-2012, (5 folders) (Box 429)
    - Staff, 1997, 1987-2003, 2012
    - Weekly management
      - 1978-1990, (5 folders)
      - 1991-2013, undated, (11 folders) (Box 430)
  - Memoranda of cooperation, 1997 (Box 431)
  - Mid-year management review, 2009
  - Military Reform Project See Containers 504-505, Smith Richardson Foundation
  - Miscellany
    - 1972-1983, (5 folders)
    - 1984-1994, (8 folders) (Box 432)
    - 1995-1996, (6 folders) (Box 433)
    - circa 1996
    - 1997, (3 folders); (1 folder) (Box 434)
    - circa 1997
    - 1998-2001, (8 folders)
    - 2002-2009, (7 folders) (Box 435)
    - 2010, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box 436)
    - 2011-2013, (7 folders)
    - 2000s
    - Undated, (3 folders) (Box 437)
  - National Charities Information Bureau
    - 1977-1983, (5 folders)
    - 1984-1988 (Box 438)
  - National Coalition for Growth, 1980-1981, (4 folders)
  - National Empowerment Television, 1991-1998, (4 folders)
  - National Heritage Foundation, 1977-1982, undated
  - National Strategy Information Center, 1979-1984, 1991-1993, undated (Box 439)
  - Notes and jottings, 1976-2012, undated, (3 folders)
  - Opportunity budget, 1998
  - Organization charts, 1976, 1984, 1997
  - Organizational procedures, undated
  - People file
    - Abrams, Elliott, 1982-1991
    - Adelman, Kenneth, 1982
    - Allen, Meg, 2009-2012
    - Allen, Richard V. ("Dick")
      - 1978-1981
      - 1982-1995, (7 folders) (Box 440)
      - 1996-2001, (3 folders) (Box 441)
    - Allison, Douglas F., 1998-2013, (2 folders)
    - Allison, Wick, 1987-1991
    - Anderson, John Bayard, 1974-1980
    - Apple, Terry, 2000
    - Archibald, George, 1989-1993 (Box 442)
    - Arnn, Larry P., 2002-2012, (2 folders)
    - Ayau, Manuel F., 1978-1997
    - Bailey, Norman A., 1983
    - Beall, Joseph E., 2001-2008
    - Bell, Belden, 1978-2012, (3 folders)
    - Bennett, William J., 1987-2006, (3 folders) (Box 443)
    - Blackburn, Benjamin B., 1979-1987
    - Brown, David R.
      - 1979-1998, (3 folders)
      - 1999-2003, (2 folders) (Box 444)
    - Buckley, James L., 1978-1980
    - Buckley, William F., Jr., 1978-2008, undated, (2 folders)
    - Busby, Horace W., 1980
    - Bush, George, 1983-1992, (2 folders)
    - Bush, George W., 1999-2010 (Box 445)
    - Bush, Jeb, 1995-2000
    - Campbell, W. Glenn, 1984, 1994-2001, (2 folders)
    - Carlisle, Margo, 1978-1982
    - Chan, Anson, 2002-2010
    - Chao, Elaine L., 2000-2005
    - Chitester, Robert J., 1980-1985
    - Chung, Ju-yung, 1991, 2001 (Box 446)
    - Clawson, Delwin Morgan ("Del"), 1974
    - Coors, Holland Hanson ("Holly"), 1991-2007
    - Coors, Joseph, 1974-2005, (3 folders)
    - Coors, W. Grover, 1991-1998
    - Coors, William K., 1997
    - Crane, Philip M., 1973-1984, 1999-2009, (7 folders) (Box 447)
    - Crozier, Brian
      - 1980-1993
      - 1994-1997 (Box 448)
    - Curtis, Carl T., 1979-1982
    - Davis, Shelby Collum, 1979-1995, (3 folders)
    - Decter, Midge
      - 1981-2003, (2 folders)
      - 2004-2012 (Box 449)
    - Dee, Robert F., 1982-1990
    - Dehmlow, Louis, 1974-1975
    - Durant, William Clark, 1974-1975
    - Eckerd, Jack M., 1979-2002
    - Ellick, Thomas C., 1979-1980
    - FitzGerald, William H. G., 1995-2006
    - Fluor, J. Robert, 1980-1981
    - Flynn, Raymond L., 1994-1995
    - Forbes, Malcolm S., 1990
    - Forbes, Steve, 2001-2012
    - Fowler, Henry H. ("Joe"), 1996-2001 (Box 450)
    - Friedman, Milton (1912-2006), 1980-2007, undated
    - Frisby, Owen V., 1979
    - Gelb, Bruce V., 1989-1991
    - Gingrich, Newt, 1981-2010, (2 folders)
    - Goeglein, Timothy S., 2011
    - Haig, Alexander Meigs, 1977-1981, 1986, (1 folder) (Box 451)
    - Hapsburg, Otto von, 1966, 1979-1990, 2003-2010
    - Harlow, Bryce Nathaniel, 1979-1984
    - Haseler, Stephen, 1981-1984
    - Hayek, Friedrich A. von
      - 1974-1992, (2 folders)
      - 1998-1999, (1 folder) (Box 452)
      - 2000-2007
    - Heatherly, Charles L., 1979-1980
    - Her, Hwa-pyung, 1982-1988, 1996
    - Herrick, Todd W., 2007-2012
    - Hume, William J. ("Jerry"), 1992-2012, (3 folders)
    - James, Kay Coles, 2002-2011 (Box 453)
    - Kemp, Jack (1935-2009)
      - 1978-2001, (5 folders)
      - 2002-2009, undated (Box 454)
    - Keys, Joseph A., 1979-1992
    - Kim, Seung-young, 2004-2007
    - Kirk, Russell, 1953, 1976, 1981-1995, 2009
    - Kissinger, Henry, 1995-2013
    - Kleintobe, Lee, 2002-2013
    - Korologos, Tom Chris, 1980-2013, (2 folders)
    - Krieble, Nancy, 1997-2001
    - Krieble, Robert Henry, 1979-1997, (4 folders) (Box 455)
    - La Force, James Clayburn ("Clay"), 1977-1982
    - Larry, Richard ("Dick"), 1989-1999, (2 folders)
    - Lee, Ki-ho, 2002-2005 (Box 456)
    - Lefever, Ernest W., 1981-1988, (4 folders)
    - Lehrman, Lewis E., 1980-2008, (3 folders)
    - Likhatchev, Slava, 2006-2008 (Box 457)
    - Lipsett, Donald J.
      - 1975-1992, (5 folders)
      - 1993-1997, (4 folders) (Box 458)
    - Lofton, John D., Jr., 1981-1982
    - Lomas, Bernard T., 1983-2011
    - Luce, Clare Boothe, 1985-1987
    - Manne, Henry G., 1974-1983, (2 folders)
    - Martino, Antonio, 1983, 1993-2012, (2 folders) (Box 459)
    - Meese, Edwin
      - 1980-1988, (5 folders)
      - 1989-2008, (2 folders) (Box 460)
    - Middendorf, John William, 1983-2012, (3 folders)
    - Moffat, Abby, 2008-2011
    - Nazari, Nersi H., 2006-2012
    - Neiland, Edward, 1998-2000
    - Newton, Hugh C., 1976-1980 (Box 461)
    - Noble, Edward E., 1973-1987, (2 folders)
    - Oliver, Daniel, 1998-2012
    - Parvin, C. Landon, 1994-1996
    - Pejovich, Svetozar ("Steve"), 1979-1991, (2 folders)
    - Pennington, Robert, 2009-2012 (Box 462)
    - Plunk, Daryl, 1999-2000
    - Pratt, Larry, 1975
    - Quayle, Dan, 1989-1992
    - Reagan, Ronald, 1978-2004, (2 folders)
    - Regnery, Henry, 1976-1987
    - Rench, J. Frederic ("Fritz")
      - 1979-1994, (3 folders)
      - 1995-2012, (2 folders) (Box 463)
    - Rhatican, Bill, 1979-1980
    - Rhodes, Thomas L. ("Dusty"), 1993-1999
    - Richardson, Warren, 1972, 1981
    - Rockefeller, David, Jr., 1981
    - Roe, Shirley, 2000-2005
    - Roe, Thomas Anderson
      - 1985-1992, (2 folders)
      - 1993-2000, (2 folders) (Box 464)
    - Rumsfeld, Donald, 1982-1988, 1995-2012, (2 folders)
    - Ryder, Richard, 1980
    - Saulnier, Raymond J., 1977
    - Saunders, Thomas A., III
      - 2004-2008
      - 2009-2012, (2 folders) (Box 465)
    - Scaife, Richard M.
      - 1985-2003, (4 folders)
      - 2004-2012, (2 folders) (Box 466)
    - Schneider, William J., Jr., 1977-1978, 1989-1992
    - Schuettinger, Robert Lindsay, 1987-2009, (2 folders)
    - Schultz, Harry D., 1980-1991
    - Schwarz, Jürgen H., 1978-1983
    - Shakespeare, Frank J.
      - 1978-1992, (2 folders)
      - 1993-1999, undated, (2 folders) (Box 467)
    - Simon, William E. (1927-2000)
      - 1959-1966, 1997-1989, (3 folders)
      - 1990-2000, (6 folders) (Box 468)
    - Simon, William E. (1951- ), 1999-2012, (2 folders) (Box 469)
    - Skinner, Samuel, 1992
    - Solomon, Norman, 1998
    - Spitzer, Arthur, 1975-1992, (3 folders)
    - Strauss, Franz Josef, 1978-1980
    - Strausz-Hupé, Robert, 1992
    - Sun, Chen, 1987-1992, 1999, undated (Box 470)
    - Thatcher, Margaret
      - 1979, 1988-2003, (5 folders)
      - 2004-2010, (4 folders) (Box 471)
    - Tracy, Brian
      - 1993-2003, (2 folders)
      - 2004-2012, (2 folders) (Box 472)
    - Urban, George R., 1991-1997, (2 folders)
    - Van Andel, Jay, 1985-2004, (2 folders)
    - Van Adel-Gaby, Barbara A., 1996-2012, (2 folders) (Box 473)
    - Van den Haag, Ernest, 1979-1983
    - Wallach, E. Robert ("Bob"), 1988-1993, (2 folders)
    - Walton, Frank J., 1977-1983, (2 folders)
    - Wasserman, René, 1975-1979 (Box 474)
    - Watkins, Kenneth, 1978-1979
    - Watrin, Christian, 1979-1982
    - Wells, Marion G., 2003-2011
    - Wells, Preston A., Jr., ("Dick"), 1994-2003
    - Weyrich, Paul M., 1978-2001, 2008, undated, (3 folders)
    - Williams, Walter E., 1978-1980 (Box 475)
    - Williamson, Richard S., 1978-1984
    - Wilson, Jack G., 1977-1984
    - Wrather, Jack, 1980-1984
  - Personnel issues, 1978-1980, 1991-2003
  - Personnel placement reports for federal government and private sector, 1987-1988
  - Peterson Wealth Management, 1987
  - Phillips, Thomas W. (1835-1912), 1966, (2 folders)
  - Policy paper production queue, 2007-2011, undated (Box 476)
  - Policy Review
    - General, 1977-1999, undated, (6 folders)
    - Index, 1977-1992 (Box 477)
  - President's Club
    - Executive Committee questionnaire responses, 1992-1993
    - General, 1982-1987
    - Mailings and meetings, 1982-2011, (4 folders)
  - President's Essays
    - 1986
    - 1987-1989, (5 folders) (Box 478)
    - 1990, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box 479)
    - 1991-1993, (4 folders)
    - 1994-1997, (6 folders) (Box 480)
    - 1998-2009, (9 folders) (Box 481)